I'm going to try and spend $100 today
cuz I don't think I can do it. First,
let's go exchange the money. $1 is 3,500
Colombian pesos. Let's go blow these
guys. Starting out with two coffees with
foamed milk.
Fresh coffees with milk and this potato
thing for $3.34.
I'm doing pretty good. This is a lulada.
It is a fruit that is native to Colombia
and they made it in this fantastic drink
that cost like I don't know $6. This
pair custom-made
hand-woven
leather sandals, 18 bucks. What do we
think? Yay or nay? Zen's pack, my only
vice, 15,000 pesos. This is sancocho,
whole fried tilapia, coconut rice, some
fried plantains, a little bit of salad,
and the most fantastic little drink.
That was $13.
This is where I stay in. They got a
little rooftop pool, pergola right here,
or a pergala, whatever you say you from
the South and bro.
Are you kidding me? Mountains, beach.
What's this little hostel? Kitchen
there.
Here's the bedroom and the bathroom.
Pretty simple. $28 a night. Winner,
winner, chicken dinner. Got a full body
massage that cost $40. 80 cent beer. I
you not. I just paid 80 cents for a
beer. That's the cheapest beer I've ever
had in my life. And this little tiny
pineapple, $1.60 for a beer and a
pineapple. I was wrong. I did it.
$106.42
to live kind of like a baller in
Colombia. I'll drink an 80 cent beer to
that.